etravelreviews.com 2008-06-24

# Privacy Statement for Earth Travel Reviews

## Effective March 5, 2007

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online visitor information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested. This notice applies to all online visitor information collected on the Earth Travel Reviews Web site. The types of online visitor information collected on the Earth Travel Reviews web site are:  

  * Membership name
  * Membership password
  * Message board comments
  * Customer service emails
  * Visitor and session data recorded by server logs

Some of our online services are provided by third-party partners, specifically display advertising ([Google Adsense](http://www.google.com/adsense/ "Google Adsense")) and web site hosting ([Doteasy Technology, Inc.](http://www.doteasy.com/ "Doteasy")). These partners may collect information about you. Because Earth Travel Reviews does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information. We publish the name and comments you submit to our Message Boards where they are publicly viewable for the world to see. Your password is used solely for authenticating your identity when you log into your Message Board account.

We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.

We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.

Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13. You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by emailing us at: [privacy@etravelreviews.com](mailto:privacy@etravelreviews.com "Contact Us!  We appreciate your feedback."). We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.

You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.

To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email at [privacy@etravelreviews.com](mailto:privacy@etravelreviews.com "Contact Us!  We appreciate your feedback.")
